# JOB APPLICATION DOSSIER

**COVER LETTER & CURRICULUM VITAE** 

**THACH TU ANH** 

THACH TU ANH

49–51, Street No.1, An KhanhWard, Ninh Kieu District, Can ThoCity

+84 907 235 898

thachtuanhtctv@gmail.com

20th April 2019,

Dear Human Resource Manager,

Apply to: Medical Representative.

I hope to apply for the position of medical representative. The position seems to fit

very well with my education, experiences, and career interests.

A little introduction of myself, I graduated from Can Tho University of Medicine and

Pharmacy. My studies have included theoretical and practical courses in subjects

such as Pharmaceutical Jurisprudence and Pharmaceutical Business Management,

Pharmacognosy, Pharmacology...Besides, I also practised Departments of

Pharmacy in Can Tho Central General Hospital, Departments of Pharmacy in Can

Tho Chidren Hospital, Quality control center of Dong Thap, Imexpharm Corporation,

etc.

Also, I am experienced in working as a cosmetic seller. Iworked as a cosmetic seller

in Azos cosmetic shop which was my part-time job last year. Moreover, I understand

the position also requires a candidate who has teamwork and communications skills,

can work well under pressure and keeps learning from colleagues. These are skills I

developed in my courses.

This letter has enclosed my resume. I hope that it can fully describe my skills and

experiences. I am glad to meet you for interview section. You can contact me at +84

907 235 898 or send information to my gmail address. I will be available at your

convenience.

Thank you for your consideration.

Yours sincerely,

THACH TU ANH



# THACH TU ANH

**Apply: Medical representative** 

**♀** Female

**\*\*** +84 907 235 898

M 16<sup>th</sup> Nov 1995

⊠ thachtuanhtctv@gmail.com

**∠** 49–51, St No.1, An Khanh Ward, Ninh Kieu Dist, Can Tho City

### **ORIENTATION**

To work in an active environment where I can utilize my knowledge and skills: communication skill, individual work and teamwork, quick adaptation to change in a high-pressure work environment. I believe that my experiences, soft skills, enthusiasm will effectively contribute to the growth of the company.

### **EDUCATION**

Oct 2014 - July 2019

# **Can Tho University of Medicine and Pharmacy**

Major: Pharmacy

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sep 2015 - Mar 2018

### Part-time Sales Staff (AZOS shop)

### Main responsibilities

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, forums...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries directly.
- Storage checking.

### **Experience**

- Always keep my knowledge up to date, developed market awareness.
- Negotiation and potential customers seeking skills improved.
- Practice meticulousness.

### **Achivement:**

Reached sales aim in 3 consecutive months.

### **ACTIVITIES**

Nov 2015 - Sep 2017

# **Consultant(University Youth Union Consultant)**

### Main responsibilities

- As a consultant, I usually inform students about Youth Union activities in the university while also remind other members to accomplish their duties.
- I'm also a supporting source in many University
  Youth Union activities.

# **Experience**

- Improve team work ability.
- There is a wide relationship with people.

### **Achivement**

Good team of University at 2017.

### **LANGUAGES**

Vietnamese and English (Certificate of English, Level B).

### **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Powerpoint.

### **SKILLS**

- Good negotiation, communication, persuasion skills.
- Responsible and respect deadlines.
- Available on urgent tasks.
- Can work under pressure.
- Decent teamwork.
- Easily adapt to new environment.
- Creative and eager for knowledge and experience.
- Can collect and classify information.
- Friendly and outgoing.

### **INTERESTS**

- Communicating, movie, listening to music, traveling.
- Reading health books.